Abdallah Ibrahim

Mobile: (+20) 1124093527

E-mail: abdallanasr505@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/M45CJ3J

Xing: https://www.xing.com/profile/Abdallah_lbrahim13/cv

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdallah-ibrahim-0a2b15156/

Objective Overview:

I am offering 2.5 years of experience in the web developing field (Full Stack Backend Mainly), College graduate seeking a technical position. Extensive technical experience at NTI. Motivated, enthusiastic and committed to be an added value employee at my work.

Personal Data:

Name: Abdallah Nasreldin Abdelrahman Ibrahim

Date of Birth: August, 14, 1994

Nationality: Egyptian

Interests: Traveling, playing tennis and Music

Work experience:

- I work as PHP Laravel developer For RayaGate in Landsberger Allee 56A 10249 Berlin,
 Deutschland from Mar 2023 till Now
- I work as PHP Laravel developer For JoSqual in Jordan from Feb 2023 till Mar 2023 Leaved because its way to manage its projects non-suitable for me.
- I work as PHP Laravel developer For Resultier in twinsfall, Idaho USA from Apr 2022 till Dec 2022

Leaved due to layoff

• I worked as PHP Laravel developer as freelancer from Sep 2020 till Apr 2022 Leaved it because of instability of monthly income and to gain more experience

• I worked as PHP developer for Euro assist form Jan 2019 till May 2019 and from Feb 2020 till Aug 2020

Leaved it due to its closing because of COVID-19

Developing the website of the company and managing its admin panel.

• I worked as Call center agent for Vodafone Egypt Sep 2016 till Oct 2018

Internships:

I was a trainee for Ipda3 tech for 3 Month as a Web Developer. From Nov 2019 till Jan 2020

I could Build 2 project by Laravel 5.8 and API by postman.

Education:

• Nano degree in angular framework

from Udacity

from Jul 2022 till Aug 2022

Graduation Project: Ecommerce Cart and products show

• Diploma in internet of thing

from information Technology Institute (ITI) (https://www.iti.gov.eg/)

From Jan 2021 till May 2021

My Graduation Project was about a public transportation. It got the third place between all graduation projects in Graduation.

• Diploma in web Development (full stack web development PHP &Laravel):

from National Telecommunication Institute (NTI) (https://www.nti.sci.eg/)

from May 2019 till October 2019 :good grade

Graduation Project: booking system we could by it book service and knows how many time

it Duarte. could get the 1st place between all projects

Bachelor of Business Administration

Faculty of commerce. Cairo University, June 2016 – good grade

Technical Skills:

Based on my Technical experience:

front end => Angular , Bootstrap

Back end => php/laravel and js /node.js

Databases => Mysql and Mongo DB

OS =>Linux (admin |), macOS

CI/CD => Git & Github

Familiar with Devops (AWS) & microservices & Agile methodology (ClickUp & twillo)

Testing => TDD / PHP Unit

Ability to deal with 3rd party API(including payment methods and gateways)

Algorithms & data structure & Design pattern

SOLID & OOP

MOT (master of things platform) and Google Cloud platform
Connecting sensor to platform using Mqtt protocol
ERD (entity relation diagram)

CS50 from edx Harvard University

Soft Skills:

Based on my work experience & NTI and university life:

- Showing Empathy
- Quick thinking & Problem solving
- Time management: gained from my pervious and current Work.
- Team work: gained from my social work within my study in the university.
- Work under stressing: gained from my previous Work.
- Multitasks and developing myself continuously .

Special Training Courses:

- ICDL course Russian cultural Center summer 2014
- General English Course British council summer 2015
- General German Course Goethe Institute winter 2018

Special Skills:

Linguistic skills:

- 1. Arabic: Mother tongue.
- 2. IELTS band 6.5 (academic).
- 3. B1 certificate at German language (note 3).